(Sheldon:)You know, it just
occurred to me,
(Sheldon:)if there are an infinite
number of parallel universes,
(Sheldon:)in one of them,
there's probably a Sheldon
(Sheldon:)who doesn't believe
parallel universes exist.
(Leonard:)Probably. What's your point?
(Sheldon:)No point.
(Sheldon:)It's just one
of the things
(Sheldon:)that makes one of
the mes chuckle.
(Sheldon:)What makes you
chuckle, Leonard?
(Leonard:)Hmm, recently?
(Leonard:)Not much.
(Sheldon:)Is it because of the
conflict that arises
(Sheldon:)from your desperate need
to pair-bond with a woman,
(Sheldon:)and the apparent collective
decision of all womankind
(Sheldon:)to deny you
that opportunity?
(Sheldon:)Um...
(Leonard:)Shut up.
(Leonard:)You know,
when my grandfather died,
(Sheldon:)and Meemaw was alone,
my mom arranged for her
to visit a center
three times a week
(Sheldon:)where she could socialize
with other lonely people.
(Sheldon:)It's very nice.
(Sheldon:)They discuss current events,
play bridge, get a hot meal.